Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.14
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Campaign for U.S. Senate, 1991; XIV.
  - Kirkpatrick and Lockhart (K & L), 12.
    - Correspondence
      - Event Correspondence, September, 1991-March, 1992 (Box 956, Folder 10-12)
      - Event Regrets, 1991-1992 (Box 956, Folder 13-14)
      - Event Regrets, 1991-1992 (Box 957, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 957, Folder 2-3)
      - Chronological Correspondence, September, 1991-February, 1992 (Box 957, Folder 4-6)
      - Alphabetical Correspondence: A-C, 1991-1992 (Box 957, Folder 7-9)
      - Alphabetical Correspondence: D-Z, 1991-1992 (Box 958, Folder 1-18)
    - Post-election Schedules and Events
      - Long range schedules, November 11, 1991-April 5, 1992 (Box 958, Folder 19)
      - Conference on "Doing Business in Central and Eastern Europe," keynote address by Dick Thornburgh, Pittsburgh, PA, November 12, 1991 (Box 958, Folder 20)
      - Vatican Conference on Drug and Alcohol Abuse, address by Dick Thornburgh, Rome, Italy, November 23, 1991 (Box 959, Folder 1-2)
      - Pennsylvania Society Ninety-third Annual Dinner, New York, NY, December 14, 1991 (Box 959, Folder 3)
      - Annual meeting of the Washington Metropolitan Area Corporate Counsel Association, luncheon address on civil justice reform by Dick Thornburgh, Washington DC, January 14, 1992 (Box 959, Folder 4-5)
      - Oxford Union Society debate, "This House Believes that British Citizens Need a Bill of Rights," Oxford, England, folder 1, January 30, 1992 (Box 959, Folder 6-8)
      - Pittsburgh Legal Spectrum conference and trade show, "Choosing Public Service," with address by Dick Thornburgh, Pittsburgh, PA, February 6, 1992 (Box 959, Folder 9)
      - Cancelled events--after nomination as Under-Secretary General of the United Nations; letter to K&L re leaving firm for one year, January-April, 1992 (Box 959, Folder 10)
    - Telephone Logs
      - September 5, 1991-February 25, 1992 (Box 959, Folder 11)